mmogah.com 2018-06-25

# Privacy Policy at Mmogah-Always Trustworthy

## Privacy Policy

[www.MmoGah.com](https://www.mmogah.com/) is aware that the security of your private information from the use of our website is an important concern. We take the protection of your personal data very seriously. Therefore, we would like you to know what data we maintain and what data we discard. With this privacy notice, we would like to inform you about our security measures.   
Collection and processing of personal data   
We collect personal data only when you provide it to us, through registration, completion of forms or e-mails, as part of an order for products or services, inquiries or requests about materials being ordered and similar situations in which you have chosen to provide the information to us. The database and its contents remain at mmogah.com and stay with data processors or servers acting on our behalf and responsible to us. Your personal data will not be passed on by us for use by third parties in any form whatsever, unless we have obtained your consent or are legally required to do so. We will retain control of and responsibility for the use of any personal data you disclose to us. Some of this data may be stored or processed at computers located in other jurisdictions, such as the United States, whose data protection laws may differ from the jurisdiction in which you live. In such cases, we will ensure that appropriate protections are in place to require the data processor in that country to maintain protections on the data that are equivalent to those that apply in the country in which you live.

#### Purposes of Use

The data we collect will only be used for the purpose of supplying you with the requested products or services or for other purposes for which you have given your consent, except where otherwise provided by law.   
What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * To personalize your experience   
(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)
  * To improve our website   
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)
  * To improve customer service   
(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)
  * To process transactions   
Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested by the customer.
  * To send periodic emails   
The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional www.mmogah.com news, updates, related product or service information, etc.
**Note:** If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email
  * To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature

####  Choice and Opt-Out

If you no longer wish to receive the mmogah.com's promotional communications, you may "opt-out" of receiving them by following the instructions included in each communication or by e-mailing the mmogah.com at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

#### Privacy Policy Mmogah is committed to protecting your privacy and safeguarding the privacy of your personal data.

We recognize the importance of protecting the confidentiality of personal information and take appropriate measures to protect your privacy as well as your personal information. We use the personal information to provide you with better customer support and services. How We Collect Information When you register we ask for information such as your name, email address, Street Address, ZIP code, and so on. When you register with Mmogah and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us. Personally Information Security Mmogah treats data as an asset that must be protected and use lots of tools to protect your personal information against unauthorized access and disclosure. Mmogah does not rent, sell, share or disclose any personally information (such as your name, address, telephone number or e-mail address) collected online on Mmogah' sites with other unaffiliated companies or organizations for not Mmogah marketing purposes.

How We Use Information Mmogah uses the personal information we collect online principally to provide you with the services you have ordered. Mmogah collects personal information to verify the accuracy of your name, billing address, shipping address, credit card number, and credit card expiration date provided, to bill you for products and services purchased and to pay you for products and services sold. Mmogah uses your e-mail address to contact you regarding the status of your order when necessary and to send you a Receipt Purchase/Sale Confirmation and Order Shipping Notification. Mmogah may occasionally let you know some information on products, services, special deals and promotions which may be of interest to you.

Account Protection Your password is the key to your account. Use unique numbers, letters and special characters, and do not disclose your Mmogah password to anyone. If you do share your password or your personal information with others, remember that you are responsible for all actions taken in the name of your account. If you lose control of your password, you may lose substantial control over your personal information and may be subject to legally binding actions taken on your behalf. Therefore, if your password has been compromised for any reason, you should immediately notify Mmogah and change your password.

All content copyright © 2006-2018 Mmogah.com. All rights reserved.
